{
    "id": "70af4822c50045b1ba9075826d3710b5",
    "title": "Present continuous or present perfect continuous",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "06ec3ff3b8e84223887ac425aada05a3",
            "title": "Present Continuous Or Present Perfect Continuous Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "It …………… continuously since the morning.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is raining",
                        "has been raining",
                        "was raining"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………… him only once.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "am meeting",
                        "have met",
                        "have been meeting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ……………….. him for a long time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "did not see",
                        "have not seen",
                        "does not see"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The children are hungry. They ……………… in the garden.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "played",
                        "are playing",
                        "have been playing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We ……………… each other since our school days.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "knew",
                        "have known",
                        "have been knowing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… you ………………… the job?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Have, completed",
                        "Are, completed",
                        "Have, been completing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her health …………….. considerably since she returned from the hills.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has improved",
                        "is improving",
                        "has been improved"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We …………………. to find our way home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have managed",
                        "managed",
                        "have been managing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Those who ……………. their work are free to go home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "finished",
                        "have finished",
                        "have been finishing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is the fifth time you ………………… that question.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "asked",
                        "have asked",
                        "are asking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}